(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will begin shortly.
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
Attention: To all attendees
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Vocal cheering is permitted.
受注生産グッズ 1
Made-to-Order Goods 1
受注生産グッズ 2
Made-to-Order Goods 2
受注生産グッズ 3
Made-to-Order Goods 3
受注生産グッズ 4
Made-to-Order Goods 4
宝鐘マリン危機一発
Houshou Marine Pop-up Pirate
宝鐘マリン 1/7スケールフィギュア
Houshou Marine 1/7 Scale Figure
宝鐘マリン プロデュース香水！
Perfume produced by Houshou Marine!
マリンタワーコラボ
Marine Tower Collaboration
Sponsors 協賛
Sponsors
最近行ったのよ、カラオケ。
I went to karaoke recently.
なんかさ、2時間で解散と思うじゃん。
Like, you'd think it's over after two hours, right?
そっからなのよ。
But that's where it really begins.
いろんなことできるわけ。
You can do all sorts of things.
ヤバイぞ。
It's insane.
PLAY! NEW (X). X PARK
X PARK 最高。
X Park is the best.
JOYSOUND X1.
宝鐘マリン 限定プライズが順次展開中！
Houshou Marine limited edition prizes are rolling out!
対象機に500円投入で、オリジナルショッパーを1枚プレゼント！
Insert 500 yen into a qualifying machine to get an original shopper bag!
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
Attention: To all attendees
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK
宝鐘マリン1stライブ 受注生産グッズ
Houshou Marine 1st Live - Made-to-Order Goods
宝鐘マリン危機一発
Houshou Marine Kiki Ippatsu (Pirate Pop-up)
宝鐘マリン 1/7スケールフィギュア
Houshou Marine 1/7 Scale Figure
宝鐘マリン プロデュース 香水！
Houshou Marine Produced Perfume!
マリンタワーコラボ
Marine Tower Collaboration
Ahoy!! キミたちみんなパイレーツ♡
Ahoy!! You're All Pirates!!
宝鐘マリン1stライブを応援しています！
I'm supporting Houshou Marine's 1st Live!
マリン船長、ソロライブ開催おめでとうございます！
Captain Marine, congratulations on holding your solo live!
マリン船長大好き！ライブ楽しんでください！
I love you, Captain Marine! Enjoy the live!
1stライブ開催おめでとうございます！応援しています！
Congratulations on your 1st live! I'm supporting you!
マリン船長！1stソロLiveおめでとうございます！
Captain Marine! Congratulations on your 1st solo live!
Attention
ご来場のお客様へ
To all visitors
受注生産グッズ 1
Made-to-order Goods 1
受注生産グッズ 2
Made-to-order Goods 2
受注生産グッズ 3
Made-to-order Goods 3
受注生産グッズ 4
Made-to-order Goods 4
宝鐘マリン危機一発
Houshou Marine: Barrel of Fun
宝鐘マリン 1/7スケールフィギュア
Houshou Marine 1/7 Scale Figure
宝鐘マリン プロデュース香水
Houshou Marine Produced Perfume
マリンタワーコラボ
Marine Tower Collaboration
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Sponsors
協賛
宝鐘海賊団船長 宝鐘マリン
Houshou Pirate Crew Captain: Houshou Marine
宝鐘マリン プロデュース 香水
Perfume Produced by Houshou Marine
宝鐘マリン × U-TREASURE
コラボジュエリーが発売決定！
Houshou Marine × U-TREASURE
Collaboration jewelry will be released!
宝鐘マリン スケールフィギュア化！！
Houshou Marine scale figure announced!!
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will start shortly
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
Attention to all guests
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援OKです
Please beware of flashing lights.
Cheering loudly is OK.
受注生産グッズ 1
Made-to-Order Goods 1
宝鐘マリン危機一発 予約受付中！
Houshou Marine Crisis One-shot pre-orders now open!
マリンタワーコラボ 開催決定！
Marine Tower Collaboration announced!
本日は宝鐘マリン1stライブ「Ahoy!! キミたちみんなパイレーツ♡」にご来場いただきまして、誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you very much for coming to Houshou Marine's 1st Live, "Ahoy!! You're All Pirates♡," today.
開演に先立ちまして、お客様にご注意ならびにご案内申し上げます。
Before the show starts, we would like to provide you with some precautions and information.
公演中の撮影・録音・録画機材の使用は、固くお断りいたします。
The use of cameras, recording, and filming equipment during the performance is strictly prohibited.
館内は禁煙となっております。喫煙はご遠慮くださいますよう、お願い申し上げます。
The building is non-smoking. We ask that you please refrain from smoking.
万が一、体調に異変を感じる場合は、無理をせず係員へお申し出ください。
In the unlikely event that you feel unwell, please do not push yourself and inform a staff member.
アホイ！ホロライブ3期生、宝鐘海賊団船長の宝鐘マリンです！
Ahoy! I'm the Captain of the Houshou Pirates, Hololive 3rd Gen, Houshou Marine!
ちょっと長いけど、キミたち、まだ注意事項があるから、ちゃんと聞くんだぞ！
It's a bit long, but my crew, there are still some rules, so listen up!
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、肩車、
Moshing, diving, and shoulder rides inside the venue,
ステージ上に物を投げ込む、ステージ上に上がる、
throwing things onto the stage, climbing onto the stage,
故意に通路をふさぐ、前に押し寄せる、
intentionally blocking aisles, or rushing forward,
周りのお客様のご迷惑となるような不自然なコール、奇声。絶対にしないってマリンとの約束だぞ！
unnatural chanting or screaming that disturbs others. Promise Marine you won't do any of those!
あと公演の妨げとなる大きな音を鳴らすなどの行為、
Also, acts such as making loud noises that interfere with the show,
不自然なタイミングで両手を左右に激しく振る、
violently waving both hands from side to side at unnatural timings,
腕を振り回す、上半身を反らすなどの過激な応援行為、
extreme cheering such as swinging arms or arching your back,
過度なジャンプ行為など、他の一味のみんなに迷惑がかかる危険行為は一切禁止です！
and excessive jumping or other dangerous acts that trouble the crew are strictly prohibited!
う、海夫先輩！ちょ、ちょっと待ってください！
U-Umio-senpai! W-Wait a minute!
マリンのクソみたいな物真似やめてください！本物のマリンが続きを読みます！
Stop that crappy imitation of Marine! The real Marine will read the rest!
本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入ってるぞ、君たち！
There are cameras in the venue for video streaming and photography, everyone!
客席のお客様の様子が映り込む場合がございます。君たち映っちゃうよ！
You guys might be caught on camera! You're gonna be on screen!
これらの映像や写真はプロモーション等に使用される可能性がございますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
Please be aware that these videos and photos may be used for promotional purposes.
お前も偽物じゃねーか！そんなことないよ、違うよぉ！
You're a fake too! That's not true, I'm not!
行くよ！せーの！それでは、まもなく開演いたします！お席についてお待ちください！
Here we go! Ready, set... We're about to start! Please stay in your seats!
無罪
Innocent
宝鐘マリン
Houshou Marine
白上フブキ　大神ミオ　天音かなた
Shirakami Fubuki, Ookami Mio, Amane Kanata
戌神ころね　白銀ノエル　雪花ラミィ
Inugami Korone, Shirogane Noel, Yukihana Lamy
Ahoy!! キミたちみんなパイレーツ♡
Ahoy!! You're All Pirates♡
Ahoy! キミたちみんな、いくよー！
Ahoy! Everyone, here we go!
海賊ならヤッホー　踊れ叫べヤッホー
If you're a pirate, Yo-ho! Dance and shout, Yo-ho!
さあ、今　旗の下へ
Now, under the flag,
宝鐘海賊団だー！
it's the Houshou Pirates!
出航！
Set sail!
踊るAhoy!に　見るAhoy!
Dancing Ahoy! Watching Ahoy!
全速前進だー！
Full speed ahead!
進め！
Advance!
今日も颯爽　大航海日和だ
Today is a dashing day for a great voyage
歌え！
Sing!
絶好のテンション　波の音に乗せて
Top-notch tension, riding the sound of the waves,
ドンブラコ
splish-splash
海でガールズトーク
Girls' talk on the sea,
おかわりが欲しい？
want another serving?
不慣れな航路も　キラキラ
Even on unfamiliar routes, sparkling
山もボロボロ　My House 手狭ね
Mountains are crumbling, my house is cramped,
見てて
look
あぁ、神様、いつかこのマリンを
Ah, God, please make this Marine
本物の海賊にしてください！
a real pirate someday!
錨を上げて　さあ出航だ！
Raise the anchor, now set sail!
我ら宝鐘海賊団
We are the Houshou Pirates
本末転倒　旗を揚げ
Putting the cart before the horse, raise the flag,
この海をジャックしちゃおー
let's jack this sea!
さあさあ　ついておいで
Come on, follow me,
共にヤッホーヤッホー叫ぼう
let's shout Yo-ho, Yo-ho together
あぁ、最高のキミ
Ah, the best you,
ようこそ我が船へ
welcome to my ship
Ahoy!
踊るAhoy!に　見るAhoy!
Dancing Ahoy! Watching Ahoy!
1, 2, 3, 4!
サン！ニ！イチ！ゴー！
Three! Two! One! Go!
熱く燃えろよパッション
Burn hot, passion!
想いを解き放て
Unleash your feelings!
赤くきらめくパッション
Glimmering red passion!
形から入るタイプです
I'm the type to start with the appearance!
発射１０秒前！
10 seconds to launch!
走れ！
Run!
ガチ恋でさぁ！
With your true love!
焼けも照れもはキラキラ
Burn and blush with a sparkle!
しんなり汗もしたたるいい女だけど
A fine woman dripping with supple sweat, but...
あ～、神様。船長がセンシティブだと
Oh, God... If the Captain is too "sensitive",
BANされちゃうのですね。
she'll get banned, won't she?
はにゃ～！
Ha-nya~!
歌は霊から取り戻せ
Recover the songs from the spirits!
これが宝鐘海賊団
This is the Houshou Pirate Crew!
君たちとなら辿り着ける
With you all, I can reach it!
伝説のエメラルドへと
To the legendary emerald!
よーそろー楽しんでや
Steady as she goes! Have some fun!
歌えヨーホーヨーホー足りない
Sing Yo-ho, Yo-ho! It's not enough!
あぁ　この景色
Ah, this scenery...
大切なんだよ
It's so precious to me.
宴だ宴だ　騒げよ騒げ
A banquet, a banquet! Make some noise!
踊るアホイに見るアホイ
The dancing Ahoy and the watching Ahoy!
同じアホイなら飲まなきゃ損損
If both are Ahoy, it's a loss not to drink!
掲げろ掲げた手に　粋なよーそろー！
Raise them up! A stylish "steady as she goes" with raised hands!
アホイ！アホイ！
A-HOY! A-HOY!
宝鐘マリン！
Houshou Marine!
世界で一番！
Number one in the world!
メスガキ！メスガキ！
Bratty girl! Bratty girl!
エロガキ！エロガキ！
Lewd brat! Lewd brat!
ケツドラム！
Ass drum!
おパンツ何色？
What color are your panties?
お宝お宝！
Treasure, treasure!
萌え萌え！
Moe moe!
ドドドスこい！
Do-do-do-sukoi!
船長超最高！
Captain is the absolute best!
もっともっともっと！
More, more, more!
ウフフフフ！
U-hu-hu-hu-hu!
キャシビリ！
Cash-Billy!
イヤンライチン！
Iyan-Raichin!
ダッチューノー！
Datchu-no!
もっと！もっと！もっと！
More! More! More!
チュリチュリッチュ！
Churi-churi-chu!
萌え萌えキュン！
Moe moe kyun!
出会って５秒で！
5 seconds after meeting!
あーもう！船長は君たちをそんな子に育てた覚えはありません！
Ah, honestly! I don't remember raising you all to be like that!
本当に...滅多ぞ！
Really... I'm mad!
立てば痴女、座れば娼、
Standing like a pervert, sitting like a harlot,
歩く姿はセンシティブ。
and the way I walk is just "sensitive".
夢を見ようこの船で
Let's dream on this ship.
後悔なんてさせない
I won't let you have any regrets.
君たちのおかげで私は
Because of you all,
船長になれるから
I can be the Captain.
フラフラ船長キャラ
Unsteady Captain character...
受け！
Accept it!
声をあげてさあ出航だ
Raise your voices, it's time to set sail!
我ら宝鐘海賊団
We are the Houshou Pirate Crew!
帆を颯爽とはためかせて旗をあげ
Let the sails flutter gallantly and raise the flag,
この海をジャックしちゃおうぜ
let's jack this sea!
よーそろーついておいで
Steady as she goes! Follow me!
共にヨーホーヨーホー叫ぼう
Let's shout Yo-ho, Yo-ho together!
あぁ　最高の響き
Ah, the greatest sound...
今日こそ我が船
Today is the day for our ship.
宝鐘の名
In the name of Houshou,
海賊だー！
we're pirates!
それじゃあ行きますよ！全開！
Well then, here we go! Full throttle!
ドキドキしちゃって...うっ！
My heart is throbbing... ugh!
手厚いな
That's some warm support.
行きますよ！
Here I go!
ねぇ言ったよね
Hey, you said it, right?
年齢なんて関係ないってさ
That age doesn't matter.
そういう面倒くさいのも含めて
That you'd love even those troublesome parts...
愛してくれるって　ねぇ、ねぇ言ったよね
Hey, hey, you said you would, didn't you?
言ってない？　ふん、そういうこと言うんだ。
You didn't? Hmph, so that's how it's gonna be.
ちなみにこの船では美少女無罪が適用されますので
By the way, "Beautiful Girl Innocence" applies on this ship!
待たせて魔法で若返り
I kept you waiting, but I've rejuvenated with magic.
秘密の素顔は君だけに
My secret true face is for you alone...
特別ですよ？
It's special, okay?
私、いい女？
Am I a fine woman?
皆とじゃなきゃ
If I'm not with everyone,
はしゃげないわ　近頃はね
I can't cut loose these days.
宝の島に
To the island of treasure...
してほしい君
you want to make me yours.
優雅で厳しさマリアージュ
A marriage of elegance and severity.
君の一番目指して
Aiming to be your number one,
よーそろー
Steady as she goes!
本当は自信ないけど
I'm actually not confident, but...
頑張っちゃう
I'll do my best!
グーグーグー
Goo, goo, goo!
最高にハッピーに包むからさ
Because I'll wrap you in ultimate happiness.
伝説になっちゃうわ
It's going to become a legend...
大人の時間
An adult time.
ドキドキしちゃって...うっ！
My heart is throbbing... ugh!
まだ、早い...
It's still too early...
だ、だ、ダメですか？
I-I-Is it no good?
フリルの服着たら...そんなことないよ
If I wear frilly clothes... That's not true!
だ、だ、だって魔法少女になってみたい
B-B-Because I want to try being a magical girl!
死んだらだめですよ
You mustn't die!
ピリ辛積極性
Spicy aggressiveness!
なんだってするから 見捨てないでキミたちー!
I'll do anything, so don't abandon me, guys!
もっとこっち見てみて〜!
Look over here even more!
たまにいじめてさ
Tease me sometimes,
それでもいいの
that's fine too.
年頃だもん 本気にしちゃう 嵐のなかも
I'm at that age, so I'll take it seriously. Even in a storm,
一緒に行こう!
let's go together!
ハコに詰めて びしょびしょぶる〜
Packed in a box, soaking wet blue~
アレレ どうした面倒くさい なんて言っちゃって
Ara-re, what's wrong? "How bothersome," I say.
叶えてあげる 君の願いを
I'll grant your wish.
ギュン ギュン ギュルン ギュン ギュン ギュルン
Gyun gyun gyurun, gyun gyun gyurun,
優しくしてね 17歳
be gentle with me, I'm 17 years old.
飛び込んでけ 前地に お楽しみ中
Dive in, front floor, in the middle of having fun.
ドキドキしてね U〜!
Make your heart throb, U~!
ああ、お許しください
Ah, please forgive me.
このマリンの魅力、魔力、不可抗力!
This Marine's charm, magical power, irresistible force!
罪な女ね
What a sinful woman.
だまってないで 捕まえてて
Don't stay silent, catch me.
世界一の お宝見せてあげるから
Because I'll show you the world's greatest treasure.
ギュッと合わせて びしょびしょぶる〜
Hold tight, soaking wet blue~
君の一番 目指してよ お宝
Aim to be your number one, because I'm a treasure.
そうだもん 大好きだって 真剣よ
That's right, I'm serious when I say I love you.
ギュン ギュン ギュルン ギュン ギュン ギュルン
Gyun gyun gyurun, gyun gyun gyurun,
恋する気持ち 17歳
feelings of love, 17 years old.
踏み込んでけ 全力 お楽しみ中
Step in with all your might, in the middle of having fun.
ドキドキしてね U〜!
Make your heart throb, U~!
しーっ! まだ早い
Shh! It's still too early.
マリン... じゃなくて
Not Marine...
マリン船長だー!
but Captain Marine!
Ahoy!! キミたちみんなパイレーツ♡
Ahoy!! You Are All Pirates ♡
キミハイ歌謡祭
Kimihai Song Festival
脱ぎ捨てられる 雑誌のように
Tossed aside like a magazine,
私のフェチが めくられるたびに
every time my fetishes are flipped through,
放り出されて しまうのかしら
I wonder if I'll be thrown out.
それが知りたくて とても
I really want to know that.
あなたの瞳の 奥に旅してく
Traveling deep into your eyes,
私なの センチメンタル・ジャーニー
it's me, a Sentimental Journey.
蕾のままで 夢を見ていたい
I want to keep dreaming while still a bud,
カゲロウのように 美しい
as beautiful as a heat haze.
物語だけ 見ていたいわ
I only want to see the story.
マリンはまだ 17だから
Because Marine is still 17.
何かに誘われて
Lured by something,
あなたに攫われて
kidnapped by you,
センチメンタル...
Sentimental...
ジャーニー...
Journey...
見知らぬ国の
In a strange land
なぞなりつづみ
the mystery drums
覗き見たくなる
I want to take a peek
不思議な気持ち
at this mysterious feeling
自分自身でさえも
Even for myself,
怖いほどなの
it's almost scary
隠された恋なら
If it's a hidden love,
ずっと大事にしていた
I'll cherish it forever
もらえるのかしら
I wonder if I can have it,
わからない
I don't know
センチメンタル・ジャーニー
Sentimental Journey
扉の前で ためらいながらも
While hesitating in front of the door
背中をそっと 押されたい
I want a gentle push on my back
見ないふりして 許してね
Pretend not to see and forgive me
マリンはまだ 17だから
Because Marine is still 17
何かに誘われて
Lured by something,
あなたにさらわれて
swept away by you
何かに誘われて
Lured by something,
あなたにさらわれて
swept away by you
センチメンタル・ジャーニー
Sentimental Journey
さあ、始まりました！
Well, it has begun!
盛り上がっております、キミパイ歌謡祭！
The Kimipai Song Festival is heating up!
司会の大神ミオと…
Your host, Ookami Mio, and...
皆さん、お待たせしました。
Everyone, sorry for the wait.
いや、お待たせすぎたのかもしれません。
Or maybe it's been too long of a wait.
いつも通りの白上フブキです。そして…
The usual Shirakami Fubuki. And...
本日主役の！
Today's star!
アホイ！ホロライブ3期生、
Ahoy! Hololive 3rd Gen,
宝鐘海賊団船長の宝鐘マリンです！
Captain of the Houshou Pirates, Houshou Marine!
よっ！キミたちー！
Yo! You guys!
なんかさっき影ナレの偽物のマリンを…
Someone who thought the fake Marine in the shadow narration earlier...
本物のマリンだと思った人？
was the real Marine?
えー！？
Eh!?
偽物なんていたんですか？
Was there a fake one?
偽物いらっしゃったんですか？
A fake one was here?
偽物？えっ、嘘だよね。
A fake? Eh? You're kidding, right?
私たちの知らないところで、まさか偽物がいたなんて。
In a place we didn't know, to think there was a fake.
似てねーだろ全然！
It didn't sound like me at all!
怖いですね。
That's scary.
恐ろしい…
Horrible...
騙されんなよ！
Don't be fooled!
恐ろしいことがいらっしゃいますね。
Scary things are happening, aren't they?
あ、ついに始まりましたけども、歌謡祭。
Ah, the Song Festival has finally started.
そうなんですも、ドキドキで。
That's right, I'm so nervous.
キミたちもみんなに、みんなに、みんなに…
To all of you guys, all of you, all of you...
あ、みんなみんなみんな…
Ah, everyone, everyone...
キミ、キミ、キミたち、キミたち、キミたち…
You, you, you guys...
我々もね、やはりね。
We are too, of course.
皆さんどうも、どうも皆さん。
Hello everyone, hello.
すごいですね本日もね、こんなにたくさんのお客さんがいっぱいいて。
It's amazing today too, with so many guests here.
すみませんマリン一つ気になったんですけど。
Excuse me, Marine, I noticed one thing.
なんですか？
What is it?
マリンが、あの、例えば、座…座れば…
When Marine said, for example, "If I sit down..."
ありました、ありましたね、そういえば。
That's right, that did happen.
あの時なんか、誰か「まりは取れよ」って言ってました？
At that time, was someone saying "Take off the ball!"?
あ、確かに、聞こえましたね、確かに。
Ah, I definitely heard that.
「まりは取れよ」って聞こえてきた気がしたんですけど。
I thought I heard someone say "Take off the ball!"
言った方ちょっとサイリウム振ってみてください。
The person who said it, please wave your glowstick.
あ！そこだ！
Ah! There!
あの一味ですね。
It's that crew member.
見つけた！あの一味でございますね。
Found them! It's that crew member.
どんだけ声デケェ一人で、一人で聞こえてきた。すげぇ。
How loud was that person? I heard them alone. Amazing.
はい、すごいですね。あ、ちょっとね、ちゃんとね、見えてますよ、今すごい。
Yes, amazing. Ah, we can see you clearly now, it's great.
あのね、一旦まず、すごいね、前にね、あの、クマ…クマの格好した
Um, first of all, it's amazing, in the front, there's someone dressed as a bear...
可愛いお客様がいらっしゃいますね。
There are cute guests here.
可愛い女がいます！
There's a cute girl!
可愛い女！
A cute girl!
ちょっとファンサが、特大ファンサ今来ております。
I'm giving them some fan service, a huge fan service right now.
みんな可愛いっすよ。隣の男も可愛い。
Everyone is cute. The guy next to her is cute too.
隣の男、上の男たち、
The guy next to her, the guys above,
上の女たち…
the girls above...
いややすごいですね、みんな可愛い。
Wow, it's amazing, everyone is cute.
サイリウムすごい出てますね。
The glowsticks are really out.
会場に限らず、配信の皆さんもいらっしゃいますのでね。
Not just in the venue, we have people watching the stream too.
そうなんです、コメントのキミたち可愛いよ。
That's right, you guys in the comments are cute too.
コメントのキミたちもね、ちゃんと、ちゃんと見てますから、安心してくださいね。
You guys in the comments too, I'm watching you closely, so please be at ease.
適宜ね、拾わせていただきますから。
I'll pick up comments occasionally.
はい、「俺ら可愛いのか」との方たち… いや、可愛いと思いますよ。
Yes, people asking "Are we cute?"... Well, I think you're cute.
ま、これからね、ま、始まったばかりなんですけれど。
Well, it's only just begun.
まだまだね、たくさんゲストが…
There are still many guests...
そうですね、いらっしゃいますね。
That's right, they're coming.
そうなんです、今日たくさん呼んじゃいました。ソロライブとは一体って感じでいっぱい呼んじゃいました。
That's right, I invited many today. It's like "What even is a solo live?" with how many I invited.
いやいや素晴らしいです。昭和歌謡祭、いつもね、ゲストの方たくさんいらっしゃいますからね。
No, no, it's wonderful. The Showa Song Festival always has many guests.
そうなんです、とても楽しみでございます。
That's right, I'm really looking forward to it.
ということでね、もうここからの晴れ舞台。
So, the grand stage from here on.
もう絶対見逃すわけにはいかないじゃないですか。
We absolutely can't miss it, can we?
もちろんです。
Of course.
ということでま、会場の皆さんはもちろんなんですけど、
So, for everyone in the venue of course, but...
配信チケットは概要欄から飛べますので、お見逃しなく！
you can get streaming tickets from the description, so don't miss out!
よろしくお願いします。
Please.
最後までじっくり見てね。
Watch carefully until the end.
お願いします。
Please.
なんとね、あの、非常に良いスライですが…
Well, it's a very good slide, but...
お、チラ見せパートね。
Oh, the sneak peek part.
あら、もしや、これで、ここまでなんですね？
Oh, could it be that this is where it ends?
ここまでですか？ あら...
Is this it? Oh...
ええええええ！
Ehhhh?!
君たち、もっと言ってやって！
You guys, protest more!
そうだよね！
Right!
「えー」だよね！
You're saying "Ehh", right?
今、無料チラ見せを見ている皆さん。
To everyone watching the free sneak peek right now.
これが... 総意です。
This is... the consensus.
「えー」です。
It's an "Ehh."
そうです。「えー」ということで、はい。
Exactly. So it's an "Ehh," yes.
チラ見せで満足できないと思うので、ぜひよろしくお願いします！
I'm sure you're not satisfied with just a peek,
so please check out the rest!
お願いいたします！
Please join us!
そういえばマリンさんのさきほどのセンチメンタル・ジャーニーなんですけども...
By the way, about your performance of
"Sentimental Journey" earlier...
はい。
Yes.
なんか替え歌してらっしゃいましたね？
You were singing parody lyrics, weren't you?
え、あ、そうなんです。
Eh? Oh, yes, I was.
マリンはまだ何でしたっけ？
Marine is still... what was it?
「17歳だから〜♪」ですね。
"Because I'm 17~♪"
このKアリーナに来てまで、詐欺は良くないです。
Coming all the way to K-Arena
and committing fraud is not good.
えっ！？
What!?
良くないですよね、皆さん？
It's not good, right everyone?
詐欺だったんですか！？
Was that fraud!?
年齢詐称は良くないと思います。Kアリーナまで。
I think age misrepresentation is bad.
Especially at K-Arena.
なんか偽物がいたり詐欺ってたり、ちょっと大丈夫ですか？
Fake versions, fraud... are you sure you're okay?
いやいやいや、それが詐欺じゃなく... 君たち！
No, no, no, it's not fraud... You guys!
マリンは何歳！？ せーの！
How old is Marine!? Ready, go!
三十路！！
Thirty!!
ちょっとバラバラじゃない！？ バラバラだから！
Wait, isn't it a bit scattered!? It's all scattered!
結構バラバラですね。
It's quite scattered.
バラバラだから、一味統率したほうがいいんじゃないですか？
It's scattered, so maybe you should lead your Ichimi better?
待って、じゃあちょっと待って。
Wait, hold on a second.
今「17歳」って言った人ー！
Those who said "17 years old" just now!
はーい！
Me!
あー、いますね。
Ah, there are some.
「三十路」って言った人ー！
Those who said "Thirty"!
はーい！！
ME!!
多いだろ！！
There's too many of you!!
圧倒的に多いですね。
It's overwhelmingly many.
いや、いいですね、盛り上がって参りました。
Well, that's good, things are heating up.
さ、話も盛り上がってきたところではありますが...
Now, while the conversation is heating up...
そろそろね、次の曲の準備いたしましょうか。
Shall we prepare for the next song?
あ、そうでした、そうですよ。まだまだ曲いっぱいありますからね、君たち！
Oh, that's right. There are still plenty of songs left, you guys!
楽しみですね。
Looking forward to it.
それでは、次の曲、参りましょう！
Then, let's move on to the next song!
どうぞ！
Please!
無料パートは終了いたしました ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free part has ended. Thank you for watching!
キミパイ歌謡祭
Kimipai Song Festival
無料パートは終了いたしました
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended.
Thank you for watching!
宝鐘マリン1stライブ「Ahoy!! キミたちみんなパイレーツ♡」
Houshou Marine 1st Live "Ahoy!! You're All Pirates♡"
全編視聴はニコニコ生放送、Z-aNにて
Watch the full show on Nico Nico Live and Z-aN